discoverybenefits.com 2018-09-04

# Privacy Policy | Discovery Benefits

## Privacy Policy

The purpose of this Privacy Policy is to let you know the ways we collect, use and share information we collect through this Site. Terms not defined in this Privacy Policy are as defined in our Terms of Service.

### Scope:

This Privacy Policy does not apply to any other websites or organizations that may be linked or referred to through this Site and we are not responsible for the information practices of any third parties. We encourage you to read the privacy policy of any third party before sharing your information. For information regarding the privacy practices of your health plan or other services provider, please contact your health plan or other services provider directly.

### Protecting your Information and Security:

We work to protect your personal information from loss, misuse, or unauthorized alteration by using industry-recognized security safeguards, coupled with a range of other security procedures and practices. We maintain physical, electronic and procedural safeguards that comply with applicable laws. We use both internal and external resources to review our security procedures. If you provide information to us through this website, your sensitive information is encrypted when it is transmitted to us. “Information” means individually-identifiable, personal, or other information regarding you.

While we take certain physical, electronic and administrative measures designed to protect the confidentiality of information, due to the nature of the Internet we cannot and do not guarantee that all Information will remain secure. By submitting information to this Site, you agree that you are aware of these risks. If you do not wish to submit your information electronically, do not do so, however in such case you may not be able to make use of the full functionality of this Site. You agree that Discovery Benefits (including our affiliates and vendors, and all owners, directors, employees and agents) is not responsible for any consequence of illegal or unauthorized acts by third parties, including but not limited to hacking or similar crimes.

This Site does not monitor for or behave differently if your computer transmits a “do not track” or similar beacon or message.

Our policies permit employees to access information only on a business need-to-know basis. We educate our employees on the importance of confidentiality and customer privacy. Employees who violate our privacy policies will be subject to the disciplinary process.

We do not reveal customer information to any external organization unless we have previously informed the customer in disclosure or agreements (such as in this Privacy Policy), have been authorized by the customer, or are required by law.

We will not record personal or sensitive information when you visit our Web site unless you enter the information voluntarily.

Whenever we hire other organizations to provide support services, we will require them to conform to our privacy standards and to allow us to audit them for compliance.

We do not use or share - internally or externally - personally identifiable medical information for any purpose other than the administration of a customer's account or claim, or as disclosed to the customer when the information is collected, or to which the customer consents, or as required by law or to protect our own rights, or as otherwise permitted by this privacy policy.

### Changes to this Privacy Policy

We continue to provide this notice at the frequency required by law and will notify Site visitors of any modification at least annually. Updates will be posted on this or a similar page of this Site. We will continue to follow the policies set forth in this notice even when a customer relationship no longer exists. However, that party will no longer receive an annual notice. By using this Site you agree to the terms of this Privacy Policy including any future changes.

### Information We Collect:

We collect personal information such as your name, billing address, e-mail, and phone number when you interact with us to use our products.

We collect both online and offline information about you through other sources such as your employer and your health plan or other services provider.

We collect personal information to deliver or allow access to our products and services.

We collect information about your system as it interacts with us such as your IP address and browser information.

### Cookies and Similar Technology

We use common Internet technologies, such as cookies and Web beacons to manage our websites and services, advertising and e-mail programs.

We collect user feedback, community discussions, chats and other interactions, such as surveys.

We may obtain additional information about you, such as demographic information, from commercially available sources and we may combine this with information we have collected from you through this Site or off-line (such as through paper forms).

### Social / Forum Sections of the Website:

Certain sections or functionalities of the Site may permit you to post information that can be viewed by other website visitors. Because of the public /group nature of these sections and functionalities, information posted here is not considered confidential. We cannot control, and are not liable for, how such Information may be used or shared by others. 

### Reviewing and Changing Your Information: 

You may be able to update certain personal information online through a web portal or by calling Participant Services. To make changes online, go to Login at discoverybenefits.com.

### Right to Request Confidential Communications:

You have the right to request that we communicate with you about confidential matters in a certain way or at a certain location. For example, you can ask that we only contact you at work or by mail. To request confidential communications, you must make your request in writing to the Discovery Benefits Privacy Officer. We will not ask you the reason for your request. Your request must specify how or where you wish to be contacted. We will accommodate all reasonable requests.

### Uses:

We do not sell or rent your personal information to third parties for promotional or marketing purposes.

We do not share your personal information with anyone outside of Discovery Benefits for their promotional or marketing use without your consent.

We use your personal or financial information to provide you with information and services you request and to give you a customized interactive experience as you use our products. We may communicate with you regarding other service or product offerings provided by Discovery Benefits. We may provide notice to you of third party offerings that may be of interest to you.

We summarize and de-identify or aggregate information about you and we also combine that information with that of others in a way that does not identify you personally to understand how our products are used, to deliver products and services and to help us develop new products and services. Because non-personal Information or aggregate information does not identify who you are, we do not limit the ways we may use or share non-personal information. For example, we may share non-personal information with our affiliates, suppliers, employees and agents, other businesses, and the government.

We may use service companies to help provide you products and services who are not allowed to use your information for their own purposes.

We may use and disclose information to comply with applicable laws, regulations and legal process. We reserve the right to use information to protect and enforce our rights and those of our affiliates, vendors, users or other third parties.

We may use and disclose information collected as otherwise necessary or useful for us to conduct our business, so long as such use is permitted by law. Specific examples include: Analyzing our audience and use patterns for the Site; storing information about your preferences and allowing us to direct or customize specific content to you; recognizing you when you return to this website or speeding-up your login. We may also use and disclose information for any other purpose with your consent and/or as may be disclosed in the area of this Site where the information is collected.

We may share and transfer information specifically including personally identifiable information to any affiliate as well as in the event of a sale of assets, merger, corporate reorganization or similar transaction.

### Children's Privacy:

This Site is not intended for and may not be used by children under the age of 13. We do not knowingly collect personally identifiable information from children under the age of 13. However, parents and or guardians may submit information about their children or covered persons under the age of 13 to us. If you believe that we have received information directly from a person under13, please contact us and we will take appropriate action.

### Data Processed in United States:

By providing any information to this Site, all users, including without limitation users in the member states of the European Union, fully understand and unambiguously consent to the collection, storage, forward transfer, and processing of such information in the United States of America.

### Contact:

Discovery Benefits, Inc.   
4321 20th Avenue S.   
Fargo, ND 58103 

Phone: 866-451-3399 

Email: DBIwebsite@discoverybenefits.com 

### Effective Date: 

March 15, 2015

### Social Security Number Protection Policy: 

It is our policy to protect the confidentiality of Social Security numbers ("SSNs”) that we receive or collect in the course of business. We secure the confidentiality of SSNs through various means, including physical, technical, and administrative safeguards that are designed to protect against unauthorized access. It is our policy to limit access to SSNs to that which is lawful, and to prohibit unlawful disclosure of SSNs.
